<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2013. CMG Ltd All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~ This software is the confidential and proprietary information of CMG
  ~ ("Confidential Information"). You shall not disclose such Confidential
  ~ Information and shall use it only in accordance with the terms of the
  ~ license agreement you entered into with CMG.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="include_screenshoot_feedback_details">Send screenshot of the last page you were on</string>
    <string name="include_screenshoot_feedback">Include screenshot</string>
    <string name="privacy_information_feedback_details">How is my information stored and shared</string>
    <string name="privacy_information_feedback">Privacy information</string>
    <string name="include_data_feedback">Include system data</string>
    <string name="include_data_feedback_details">Share system data with us to better diagnose the problem.</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="newsletter_pensioner">pensioner</string>
    <string name="newsletter_employee">employee</string>
    <string name="app_name">newsletters</string>
    <string name="error_config">Please set the %1$s constant and recompile the app.</string>
    <string name="already_registered">Device is already registered on server.</string>
    <string name="gcm_registered">From GCM: device successfully registered!</string>
    <string name="gcm_unregistered">From GCM: device successfully unregistered!</string>
    <string name="gcm_message">A new version %1$s available!</string>
    <string name="gcm_newsletter_message">News! newsletter: \"%1$s\" have been uploaded</string>
    <string name="gcm_error">From GCM: error (%1$s).</string>
    <string name="gcm_recoverable_error">From GCM: recoverable error (%1$s).</string>
    <string name="gcm_deleted">From GCM: server deleted %1$d pending messages!</string>
    <string name="server_registering">Trying (attempt %1$d/%2$d) to register device on Demo Server.</string>
    <string name="server_registered">From Demo Server: successfully added device!</string>
    <string name="server_unregistered">From Demo Server: successfully removed device!</string>
    <string name="server_register_error">Could not register device on Demo Server after %1$d attempts.</string>
    <string name="server_unregister_error">Could not unregister device on Demo Server (%1$s).</string>
    <string name="options_register">Register</string>
    <string name="options_unregister">Unregister</string>
    <string name="options_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="options_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="dialog_close">Close</string>
    <!-- Action bar menu -->
    <string name="action_bar_search">Search</string>
    <string name="action_bar_add">Add</string>
    <string name="action_bar_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="action_bar_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_bar_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_bar_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="action_bar_sort_alpha">Sort alphabetically</string>
    <string name="action_bar_sort_size">Sort by size</string>
    <string name="action_bar_sort_date">Sort by date</string>
    <string name="action_bar_share_with">Share with...</string>
    <string name="action_bar_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_bar_switch_view">Switch view</string>
    <string name="action_bar_grid_view">Grid view</string>
    <string name="action_bar_list_view">List view</string>
    <string name="action_bar_carousel_view">Carousel view</string>
    <string name="action_menu_content">More</string>

    <!-- Newsletter -->
    <string name="empty_newsletter">No newsletter found</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newsletter_list">NewsletterListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment_vs_pager">Letter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab_screen">TabScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="status_download">download</string>
    <string name="status_open">open</string>
    <string name="status_downloading">downloading</string>

    <!-- About screen -->
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_description">The BP Pensions newsletter application</string>
    <string name="about_version">Version</string>
    <string name="about_manage_agent">BP Contact</string>
    <string name="about_manager">Nigel Johnson</string>
    <string name="about_develop_agent">Developed By</string>
    <string name="about_company">Claybourne McGregor (C-MG)</string>
    <string name="about_developers">developers</string>
    <string name="about_developer1">Hai Lu</string>
    <string name="about_developer2">Long Nguyen</string>
    <string name="about_project">project manager</string>
    <string name="about_project_manager">Anh Nguyen</string>
    <string name="about_test">test leader</string>
    <string name="about_test_leader">Huong Vu</string>
    <string name="about_ba">business analyst</string>
    <string name="about_ba_name">Elaine Dimon</string>
    <string name="about_agent">pdf viewer licensed by</string>
    <string name="about_cmg">Claybourne McGregor</string>

    <!-- Share screen -->
    <string name="title_activity_share">ShareActivity</string>
    <string name="share_title">Share</string>
    <string name="share_description">Scan the QR code or email share </string>
    <string name="share_link">here</string>

    <!-- Feedback screen -->
    <string name="feedback_title">Feedback</string>

    <!-- License screen -->
    <string name="title_activity_license">LicenseActivity</string>
    <string name="license_title">License</string>
    <string name="license_description">Version 1.0, January 2013</string>
    <string name="license_content">TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION\n\n
	1. Definitions.\n
									 
	"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 7 of this document.\n
									 
	"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.\n
									 
	"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, 
	"control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.\n
									 
	"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.\n
									 
	"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.\n
									 
	"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.\n
									 
	"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).\n
									 
	"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.\n
									 
	"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."\n
									 
	"Author" shall mean Licensor and Legal Entity – Claybourne McGregor Consulting Ltd.\n\n
									 
	2. Grant of Copyright License.\n Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, the Author hereby grants to You a United Kingdom, non-exclusive, license for the fixed term of 2 years ending on December 2015 to distribute the Work. No sublicense is granted. No reuse of the code or objects is granted. No reuse of design or graphics is granted. No modification to the Work is granted. No Derivative Works should be undertaken without prior agreement between Owner and You.\n\n
									 
	3. Redistribution.\n You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works without modification to Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:\n
									 
	(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work a copy of this License; and\n
									 
	(b) You must not modify any part of the Work; and\n
									 
	(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works.\n\n
									 
	4. Trademarks.\n This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.\n\n
									 
	5. Disclaimer of Warranty.\n Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.\n\n
									 
	6. Limitation of Liability.\n In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall the Author be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Author has been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n
									 
	7. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability.\n While redistributing the Work You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of the Author, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold the Author harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Author by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n\n
									 
	END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n\n
									 
	Copyright 2013 Claybourne McGregor Consulting Ltd\n\n
									 
	Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
</string>

    <!-- Help screen -->
    <string name="title_activity_help">HelpActivity</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_description">The list below details the icons and their actions:</string>
    <string name="help_newsletter">Newsletter, touch to open</string>
    <string name="help_download">Download, touch to activate</string>
    <string name="help_delete">Delete the local newsletter copy</string>
    <string name="help_progress">Download in progress</string>
    <string name="help_web">Open the main website</string>
    <string name="help_share">Share this application with others</string>
    <string name="help_help">Show this help screen</string>
    <string name="help_search">Search by title or description</string>
    <string name="help_view_grid">Display as a grid</string>
    <string name="help_view_list">Display as a list</string>
    <string name="help_view_carousel">Display as a carousel</string>
    <string name="help_sort_date">Sort by date</string>
    <string name="help_sort_az">Sort by title</string>
    <string name="help_sort_size">Sort by size</string>

    <!-- Preferences -->
    <string name="title_changelog">Changelog</string>
    <string name="preferences_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="other_preferences">Other</string>
    <string name="mainpage_preferences">Newsletter display</string>
    <string name="newsletter_category_preferences">Newsletter category</string>
    <string name="title_checkbox_newsletter_pensioner">Pensioner newsletter</string>
    <string name="summary_checkbox_newsletter_pensioner">Display pensioner newsletters on main page</string>
    <string name="title_checkbox_newsletter_employee">Employee newsletter</string>
    <string name="summary_checkbox_newsletter_employee">Display employee newsletters on main page</string>
    <string name="summary_list_view_choice">How newsletters present on main page</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_list_view_choice">Select view type</string>
    <string name="summary_list_sort_choice">How newsletters sort on main page</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_list_sort_choice">Select sort type</string>
    <string name="title_parent_checkbox_report">Send report to developer</string>
    <string name="summary_parent_checkbox_report">Help us to make your experience better</string>
    <string name="summary_child_send_errors"></string>
    <string name="title_child_send_errors">Send errors</string>
    <string name="summary_child_send_statistics"></string>
    <string name="title_child_send_statistics">Send statistical data</string>
    <!-- Book reader -->
    <string name="go_to_page">Go to page!</string>
    <string name="search_text">Search ...</string>
    <string name="page_out_of_range">Page number out of range. Valid range: 1-%1$d</string>
    <string name="crash_title">Crash Report</string>
    <string name="title_activity_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>


    <string name="error_message">We\'re very sorry to say that an unexpected error has occurred for you.\nCould you please send us feedback, so we can fix it ASAP!</string>
</resources>